MAXIM KOLOMENSKIY

Game Programmer

<u>+44(0)7501063560</u> | <u>maximbsb@gmail.com</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/maximkolomenskiy</u>

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Over 8 years of experience in C# programming within Unity, with <u>more than 15 games</u> <u>developed</u>. Recorded over <u>70 Unity tutorials</u> and created a <u>C# programming Udemy</u> <u>course with over 300 purchases</u>. Skilled in crafting unique game mechanics and solving unconventional problems that require creative thinking. Experience includes working in small teams of 2-3 people at D2D Studio and larger teams of 15 at Playwind Games as a gameplay programmer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Playwind Games | Vauxhall, London | Unity Game Programmer

Jun 2023 - Sep 2023

- Played a key role in developing front-end level mechanics and UI systems for MiiWorld a game with over 1+ million downloads on the Google Play Store.
- Incorporated GitHub and SourceTree, collaborating with a team of 15 members and maintaining project integrity, resulting in streamlined project updates.
- Contributed to daily meetings, offering ideas and suggestions to enhance game mechanics, design, and overall player experience.

<u>D2D Studio | Eindhoven, Netherlands | Game Developer</u>

Dec 2021 - Jan 2023

- Developed 8 interactive prototypes in Unity, closely following client specifications and feedback.
- Optimized game performance, achieving up to an 75% reduction in load times and improving frame rates across mobile devices and platforms.
- Collaborated within a small team (2-3 members), coordinating daily through ClickUp to establish and meet intermediate project milestones.

Eximus Education | London, England | Unity C# Tutor

Dec 2022 - May 2023

- Taught Unity and C# programming to 5 students in both Russian and English languages.
- Designed personalized lesson plans, tailored to individual student goals and areas of interest to maximize learning outcomes.
- Incorporated industry best practices, teaching students not only technical skills but also professional habits, such as code organization, testing, and collaboration.

<u>Hilton | London, England | F&B Assistant</u>

Mar 2023 - Jun 2023

- Delivered customer service to over 500 guests at large-scale events, serving drinks and addressing individual needs, ensuring a positive guest experience.
- Collaborated with a team of 8 collegues in a fast-paced environment, maintaining smooth operations during peak hours.
- Served VIP guests, providing personalized service and ensuring a high level of attention to detail for exclusive clientele.

MAXIM KOLOMENSKIY

PROJECTS

Diver Cat Independent	Oct 2024 - Present
Mii World Playwind Games Game Programmer	Jun 2023 - Sep 2023
Chicken ARMy Independent	Apr 2023 - May 2023
<u>Avia Master Independent</u>	Apr 2023 - Apr 2023
Ragdoll Fight Arena Independent	Jan 2023 - Feb 2023
Mining Race D2D Studio Game Programmer	Dec 2022 - Jan 2023
Thumb Wars D2D Studio Game Programmer	Nov 2022 - Nov 2022
<u>Unity C# Programming Course</u>	Jun 2022 - Jun 2022
Stickman Grapple D2D Studio Game Programmer	Jun 2022 - Jun 2022
Thief Birds Independent	Apr 2022 - May 2022
Flip Assassin D2D Studio Game Programmer	Mar 2022 - Apr 2022
<u>Flex Road D2D Studio Game Programmer</u>	Feb 2022 - Feb 2022
Rocket Demolish D2D Studio Game Programmer	Dec 2021 - Dec 2021
Stretchy Basketball Prototype Independent	Dec 2021 - Dec 2021
<u>Survival Game Project Independent</u>	Dec 2020 - May 2022
YouTube - Unity Tutorials	Jan 2019 - Jun 2022
Glow Ball Bounce Independent	Oct 2019 - Nov 2019
<u>Butterflying Independent</u>	May 2019 - Jun 2019

EDUCATION

<u>London South Bank University (LSBU) BA (Hons) Game Design</u>	2022 - Present
CompTIA A+ / Cyber security certification	2024 - 2024
<u>Tilburg University Entrepreneurship and Business Innovation BSc</u>	2021 - 2022
British School of Brussels (BSB) Higher Education	2015 - 2021

SKILLS

C# Programming	3D Modeling	Game UI/UX Design
Unity Engine	Game Optimization	Version Control (Git)
Physics and Math Knowledge	Al Programming	Debugging

TECHNICAL PROFICIENCIES

Unity	Blender	Unreal Engine 5
C#	Photoshop	C++
GitHub	Davinci Resolve	Python